{
    "id": "97c511219ea149599c58bc2c21d2b400",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Smoking ....................................... on the campus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has forbidden",
                "has been forbidden"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Students ............................................ to smoke on the campus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have forbidden",
                "have been forbidden"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Consulting a good doctor ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advised",
                "is advised"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You .......................................... to consult a good doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advised",
                "are advised"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Parking in front of their gate ........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is allowing",
                "allowed",
                "is allowed"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "People ......................................... to park in front of their gate.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are not allowing",
                "are not allowed",
                "not allowed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Early booking .............................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is advising",
                "advised",
                "is advised"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Passengers .......................................... to book their tickets early.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advised",
                "advising",
                "are advised"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She was made ........................................... the whole story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "repeat",
                "to repeat"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Pregnant women .......................................... to go on a diet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not advised",
                "are not advised",
                "are not advising"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}